What's wrong with you?
Our mother is dead.
Hi. I'm Eddy.
Oh. my fucking God. It's Johnny!
Because Eddy's good people
and her wife just died.
- How long ago?
- Full-on married?
Just two years.
Listen to this. Vidalia
has left us the building.
but we have to split it three ways.
- With the wife?
- Yeah. we have to sell it.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Hey. what the hell?
Get your cracker ass out of
our neighborhood. all right?
Nobody wants you here!
Pinche gringo pendejo!
Synced & corrected by reggielist
www.addic7ed.com
What the hell?
Lyn!
Lyn...
Good morning.
You know I don't do the whole
co-sleeping in bed thing.
I freaked out with my
bed by the window. I...
don't know who moved it back.
I guess they're not worried
about drive-bys anymore.
It's awful Martha Stewart's awake.
I'm sure she's a lovely human.
but. like. do we have to deal with her?
Not... not for long.
I'm meeting with that
developer to discuss options.
Do you think he. or they.
or however that works.
do you think they'll
want to buy the building?
I hope so.
Or... I mean. we can
give up our inheritance
and save ourselves a headache.
I mean. that's also an option.
Even that takes six months to probate.
What even is "probate"?
For a second when I woke up
I forgot why we were really here.
Are you coming with me?
I want to...
It's just that Juniper
flew down to get his truck.
and I have to go meet him.
Heads-up. I might spend the night.
Oh. hey.
Buenos días!
- Good morning. Eddy.
- Morning.
Something for your panza.
before you guys go out.
Los chilaquiles are a
hundred percent vegan.
Chequeé online and
everything just to make sure.
- That's so sweet.
- Yeah.
I wish we had time to. like. properly...
Mm-hm.
But you know what? Uh...
A little bite won't. you know...
Oh. my God!
These are... beyond!
I want to make sure that you are aware
that I am looking at...
different options for the building.
including a potential sale.
That's where I'm heading right now.
Thank you. um. for...
all this.
Seriously. thank you.
- So good!
- I'm sorry. but...
I don't wanna be that
person. mala gente.
but... I didn't agree to sell nothing.
And...
if I'm correct. I do
happen to own a third of it.
so I think maybe I get a say.
I think we can all sit
down and talk about it
when Emma finds out
what's going on with everything. right?
Well. I'd know better what's going on
if I could see income ledgers. expenses.
tax returns?
Just to be better informed.
Do you think I could
take a look at those?
Mm. your Ma is the
one who kept the books.
I... would have to look for them.
I'll be so grateful if you did.
But I'm not selling.
no matter what the books say.
I could never do that to Vida.
Then I'll see you in court.
This is your girl. La Pinche Chinche.
bringing you the real.
multilayered tragedy
of gentrification. mi gente.
This house. I knew the
familia that lived there.
I went to school with two of the boys.
Pero now. because their landlord
was money-hungry for them Trump dollars.
they've been displaced
to the Four Winds.
or to Norco.
but to a one bedroom
for the five of them.
But you know what the real tragedia is?
That's the real tragedia.
that you've got neighborhood people.
And no shade. okay? Because I know
everybody's gotta eat and pay that rent.
but they're the ones that
are nailing these nails
to these fucking coffins.
building these putos sideway fences!
Gentry-fences?
They make them for rich assholes
that are colonizing our hood!
Qué onda. guüey?
I... I'm sorry if I fucked that
up for you. Mari. I. uh...
I'm just really glad about what you say.
N-no. it's... it's fine.
Do you wanna finish it off?
It's... It's for my... my Vlog.
I'm doing one about
these sideway fences.
I... I know your Vlog.
I'm subscribed.
You want me to do it?
What? Oh... oh. yeah!
Well. let's take it over here.
Mm.
You ready?
Yeah.
Mi gente.
these opportunistic putos.
these corrupt city politicians
and these greedy ass developers
with their talks of
inclusive planning process...
es puro talk.
It's meant to obliterate us!
To obliterate us!
So. what you gon' do about it?
Let me tell you.
We're gonna speak up
and we're gonna use our voices
to unapologetically protect what's ours.
by any means necessary.
You feel me?
Tlaloc out.
You don't have to use
that if you don't want to.
No. I will.
It's...
It's what I was trying
to say. It's great.
Right on.
Shit. look. I-I gotta
get to school. I'm...
riding the bus these days. so...
I'll see you at Vigilante's?
Yeah. of course.
Firme.
One more. babe?
Yeah. baby.
Oh. fuck!
- Oh.
- Hey. babe.
- Did you bring a plug?
- No. f-fingers are good.
Wait. wait. wait!
Are you getting dressed already?
You expect me to stay half naked
while you break up with me?
I... I said a break.
I said I need to explore a break.
for both of us.
- Like I said.
- Could you...?
Could we not make this. that. please?
I'm sorry that I'm
making it that for you.
Come on. babe. this is already
hard enough for me as it is.
Are you serious right now?
You know. this is not
how I wanted this to...
Fuck!
The cylinder's like... jamming.
Yeah. I. look...
Hey! Babe...
I wanna be here for you.
If you need...
I don't know. if you need closure.
or something. I... I...
I wanna... You know. I
don't wanna be that guy.
Here's closure for you.
You waited to dump me
until after I ate your ass.
Whoa. wait!
That's so fucking shitty
of you to leave me with.
- You'll be fine.
- Wait! Uh...
- Lyn!
- Yes?
That's your bag.
You fucking packed my bags?
Just the one.
Alright. Lyn. look.
I don't wanna be tacky
and have to ask. but...
I'm sorry. baby. I mean...
Lyn.
Know this about yourself. Juniper.
You broke up with me two days
after I buried my mother
and that will always
be the truth about you.
Espíritu infinito.
ábrele el camino para que
le llegue la ilumuminación.
Ábrele el camino. Ilumínala. Padre.
Ábrele los ojos...
Te tronaron.
What?
Que si tu gringo broke up with you.
Oh...
Va a estar un poquito bitter.
pero it'll calm you down.
M'ijita.
Yo te lo digo. he was
not the one for you.
Yeah. you said that yesterday.
Y?
Was I right?
Pero. like. you said something else.
- You said that...
- Te dije...
that your true love has
and always will be here.
Right.
Pero that's like... confusing.
Por qué confusing?
The cards estuvieron muy clear.
Your big love está aquí. at home.
Señora. that could only mean Johnny.
that we're meant to be together.
Las cartas no dijeron nothing
about a man. mi amorcito.
- It's bigger than a man.
- But see? I don't...
I don't get it.
Could you look at your cards
and ask if Johnny still loves me?
Eso no es algo that I
have to see in the cards.
Sí. este Johnny todavía
está empelotado contigo.
Pero can you call that love?
Wait.
So... So he does love me?
Ay. Dios mío!
Sure. yes.
Thank you!
Thank you. Doña Lupe.
Gracias! Muah!
And... and... and for esto. también.
I¡No. hombre. yo sé! IEstas
pendejas nunca hacen caso!
¿Qué le vamos a hacer?
I pictured you in knee-high boots
plowing through that
Chi-Town snow by now.
Not yet.
Still things to do here. and...
I noticed you didn't treat yourself.
I don't do sweets.
That's new.
Is it?
When this was a regular panadería
you always let me buy
you orejitas after school.
Funny. I...
don't remember that.
Oh. really?
What happened?
They're good. but not as
good as the old-school ones.
Now. everything's slowly becoming
a plastic version of
what they were. right?
- Mmm. hm.
- First of all...
Almond milk. café de Goya. Like. what?
And what panadería had... tables
and Wi-Fi growing up. yeah?
Mm-hm. that's the only...
place with Wi-Fi in a
whatever block's radius.
so... I'm grateful for the upgrade.
Speaking of upgrades.
I hear you're thinking of
making a deal with Nelson.
This fucking neighborhood!
Nelson has single-handedly
transformed block after
block of this neighborhood.
You can't just hand
over your property to...
Cruz.
We're not discussing this.
Sorry. I just...
Yeah. okay.
Bueno.
back to work.
I...
I'm... right next door.
at Unidos Por East Side.
Cruz...
Thank you for this sweet thing.
Call. or text.
or smoke-signal me.
if you need anything
while you're in town. yeah?
Or when you're back in Chicago.
Cuídate.
Oh. my God. you have no toilet seat.
I had to. like. yoga squat.
Why don't you have a toilet seat?
No need. All dudes here.
I mean. but like. for clients.
You good. then?
What do you mean? Oh. yeah!
Thank you.
C'mon. I'll walk you out.
Are you okay?
Me? I'm... fine.
You don't seem fine.
- Do you wanna talk about it?
- No!
No. no. no. no. no!
You're not coming up
here doing all that!
Doing all what?
Lyn. I'm real sorry about your amá.
I mean it.
In all this.
I want you to know that
I'm sorry she's gone.
Thank you.
But I shouldn't have
gone to the velorio.
'Cause I should've remembered about you.
I should've remembered that
you'll always be a mala hierba.
C'mon.
No. I know you got used to it. Lyn.
All those times you came back
'cause of whatever asshole
up there wasn't working out.
All those times I came
back to you. like a baboso.
And every fucking time
you break my heart!
Well. I'd say that it was much
more complicated than that. Johnny.
Please!
All this time...
I'm not letting you get in there!
I ain't the same pendejo
from before. who just...
smell you and starts babeando.
I got myself a great girl
and I'm about to be a father
with her. and you know what?
I've never been happier about
nothing in my whole life.
so I'm begging you.
please. for however long you
have to be in town this time.
stay the fuck away from me!
Apá! No fuistes a diálisis?
Hoy no. m'ija.
What do you mean "Hoy no"?
You know you have to go to
get your dialysis today. Apá.
Si no. te pones real sick.
Pos Johnny nunca vino.
- What?
- Tú me haces otra cita. m'ija?
No. Apá. okay?
That'll get you out of your rotation.
Usted sabe what the doctor said!
Your call has been forwarded to an...
Okay. just put your pants
back on. voy por Johnny. okay?
I'll be right back.
Johnny!
Eres la hijita de Vi... Vidalia?
Mm-hm.
Qué pena! I am so sorry.
- Gracias.
- Yeah.
You always won the spelling.
Siempre le ganabas a mi hija. Chela.
Eras bien aplicada.
But now...
you are here. just like me.
About to lose everything.
- No. I'm...
- Pero don't feel bad. m'ija.
Son víboras.
These people.
they are sucking the blood
out of the neighborhood.
Pero sabes qué. m'ija?
In a way. this was always
going to happen to you guys.
Ever since your mother
turned... You know.
People didn't go to the bar.
I don't know how she kept
it going all those years.
Not that los Hernandez were ever known
as good business people.
Before. tampoco.
But at least. your
abuelo kept things going.
We're ready for you. Sra. Benitez.
It was nice seeing you. m'ija.
Good luck in there.
She's...
- She's really gone!
- Shit!
Mami is gone!
Shh.
Thank you. Daria.
You have to try this coffee.
It's crack!
I met these guys when they
were first brewing the stuff
out of their garage in Silverlake.
Now they got shops all over LA.
We're trying to get a
location in Cesar Chavez going.
I think people there are gonna love it.
Try it!
I came to... talk numbers.
All right.
Down to business.
I like that.
So.
it's gonna take some finagling. alright?
But I'm prepared to
twist an arm if I have to.
to get you an offer
that's gonna cover not one.
but both mortgages.
Both mortgages?
What are you talking about?
Let me show you.
You see. your mother.
may she rest in peace...
hadn't raised the rent on
these tenants for years.
Since she took it over from
your grandfather. probably.
When I first met with
her. she was having trouble
making the payments
on the first mortgage.
You know the one she took out
for all those building improvements?
And then. when she got sick.
she started having a little trouble
keeping the bar open every day.
So the bar business
started to decline...
So that's when we came in.
with a very generous offer. by the way.
for a second mortgage.
For a 110 percent of the
value of the building.
But the funny thing...
You gave my mother a predatory loan.
We owe more than the building is worth.
I... see why it might look that way.
- Mm.
- But you're a smart girl.
Well. thank you.
Think about it.
Your mother was in the thick of it.
It was a matter of survival for her.
And. to be honest.
it wouldn't be a bad idea for you
to start thinking about it that way too.
You knew Vidalia would never
be able to pay this loan back.
What I want you to focus on...
is you're a hair away from foreclosure.
But you don't want that on your record.
So look. if I can even swing
it and get you the offer
that'll cover the entire mortgage...
Emma. you take it and run.
Because no one else will
pay you anything close
to what you owe.
I wanna take care of you here.
I'll pay my mother's debt
before I ever sell to you.
In fact...
it's exactly what I'm going to do.
I thought you were staying
with Jupiter tonight.
Yeah. there's no more Jupiter.
How much are we getting for it?
It's not good.
Vida owed a ton.
She owed everything. actually.
Made a fucking mess of things.
Wait. so...
What's gonna happen. then?
We're gonna have to
stay a little longer.
until I figure out what to do.
Until I figure out
what we are going to do
with all of this.
You weren't going to say a word?
I figured you'd find out in the wash.
Is that flan still good after two days?
Well. yeah.
Flan keeps for a week.
More. sometimes.
It's gotta get eaten.
This is corn flan.
this one's chocolate
and this one's got some
weird nuts in it. so...
No está tan rico.
Oh. man!
What was. uh...
Chela's... last name?
The one I used to always
beat at the Spelling Bee.
- With the moles?
- Mm-hm.
- Benitez. I think.
- Oh. yeah!
Benitez.
Her mother is an asshole.
Oh. yeah. not a nice woman.
She made some trouble
for us here and there.
Vieja metiche.
Flan has like. milk. right?
Yeah. y eggs.
Fuck it.
God. I'd forgotten about flan!
It's impossible to be a
100 percent vegan here.
No te preocupes.
We won't tell nobody.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm